themediatrust.com 2017-04-28

# Privacy & Security | The Media Trust

### **Privacy notice**

The Media Trust ("Media Trust") is committed to the privacy of all visitors to its website. To that end, Media Trust has established this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to protect each visitor's privacy. This Policy explains what and how Media Trust collects, uses, stores and protects the information gathered from its website. By using and visiting the website, you agree to this Policy and the uses made of personal information as set forth herein or amended hereafter.

### **Collection, use and disclosure of information**

Media Trust does not collect personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide us personally identifiable information through an online form or e-mail communication or you are accessing client-specific, secure content. We may use cookies to ensure authorized access to client-specific secure content. Our use of cookies is explained in greater detail below. When accessing client-specific secure content, you are acting as a representative of your company and your interactions with Media Trust's site in this capacity are governed by our relationship agreement with your company.

Media Trust's site also automatically creates logs regarding your and other user sessions on TheMediaTrust.com, such as features that you use, the actions that you take, and the information that you access. Media Trust generally use this information in statistical and aggregate formats to assess the effectiveness of the site and to better understand your priorities and interests.

Media Trust does not sell, distribute or disclose your personally identifiable information collected from TheMediaTrust.com to third parties without your consent. However, we may release information to a third party if required by a legal process such as a subpoena or a search warrant. Please note that visitors to TheMediaTrust.com are not required to provide us personally identifiable information to use the public areas of the site. You can provide Media Trust with information such as address, e-mail address, or telephone number if you would like to learn more about Media Trust's products and services.

### **Use of cookies**

Cookies are only used when existing Media Trust clients visit the site, and not when other individuals visit the website or request other information from Media Trust. Cookies are small pieces of information transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your preferences and settings. Cookies collect information such as the type of search engine used, the sections of the website visited and other website usage information. Media Trust may use this information for research purposes and to enhance the website. The information is aggregated prior to such use and does not include any personally identifiable information.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies and you may manually disable them. For more information on disabling cookies, go to the "help" menu on your browser. The website may still be viewed after disabling cookies.

### **Data security/integrity**

Media Trust has security functions in place to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. Only authorized employees have access to the data you provided and that access is limited by need. Our employees who have access to the data you provided have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information.

### **Children's privacy**

We intend the website to be used only by adults. Children are to obtain their parents' permission prior to sending any personal information to us over the Internet. The website does not knowingly or intentionally collect information on children under the age of 13. If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has supplied personal information to Media Trust via the website without their parent's consent, that information will be deleted from our system.

### **Changes to our privacy policy**

Media Trust may change and update this Privacy Policy, including materially changing the use made of personal information described herein. Any change or update to our privacy policy will be posted on our website under "Privacy Policy" at least 30 days prior to their implementation. Your continued use of the website after the effective date of any changes will constitute your acceptance of all of the changes.

### **Contacting us**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement as it relates to your use of this site or MediaTrust's products and services, please submit a privacy inquiry.

### **Miscellaneous**

This Policy and any issue or dispute regarding privacy concerns will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Virginia, without regard to the choice of law provisions. This Policy is the entire agreement between the parties relating to privacy issues relating to use of the website and personal information collected by Media Trust.
